vinvesting.com 2007-02-26

# Privacy Policy | Vinvesting.com

### Privacy Policy

Published Mon, 2006-12-25 14:51 

We record your personal information (name, address, e-mail address) only when you voluntarily offer it. We do not sell or rent any information you submit to us. 

VInvesting.com makes use of a technology called "cookies" which stores small pieces of information on your computer. Sites often use cookies to identify repeat visitors and offer them personalized service. Our sites uses cookies to keep track of your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. VInvesting.com will only store information that adds to your browsing experience. This information is not personally identifiable. If for some reason you would rather not take advantage of the benefits made possible with cookies, most Web browsers allow you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept. Check your browser's documentation and help files, or contact your browser vendor, for more information about its cookie features.

Registration at the VInvesting.com requires a valid e-mail address. This address is used only to send you your password, and to subscribe to our 100% opt-in mailing list, if you enable that option. Cookies are used in the forum solely for the purpose of letting viewers know about new posts since their last visit, and storing their forum password if they enable that option.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve our ads on the Internet. These third-party advertising companies employ cookie and 1x1 pixel .gif technology to measure and improve the effectiveness of ads for their clients. To do so, these companies may use anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites. This information can include: date/time of banner ad shown, the banner ad that was shown, their cookie, the IP address. This information can also be used for online preference marketing purposes.

If you want to prevent a third-party advertiser from setting and/or reading cookies on your computer, currently you may either visit each ad network's web site individually and opt out or visit the NAI gateway opt-out site to opt-out of all network advertising cookies. [ Click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp) for the NAI gateway opt-out site. This site will also allow you to review the third-party advertising companies’ privacy policies.

Our servers log URLs and times of access to each page of our site, the referring URL and the IP address or hostname of the computer making the request. We use this information only to monitor the volume of traffic to the site, except in cases where we suspect a user is abusing the site's resources. In such cases, we will attempt to identify the ISP of the user and let the provider know about the abuse.

We also recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically, as VInvesting.com may update it from time to time. 

To contact us regarding our Privacy Policy, please use the contact form. **  
**
